http://www.plastics.saint-gobain.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Main MenuProducts & SolutionsBackProducts & SolutionsAll BrandsBackAll BrandsALL BRANDSBioSil®Bio-Simplex®C-Flex®CHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeCORETECH®COVISON™Dynafoam®Fluorowrap®FURON®Green Glue®KryoSure®KryoVue®Labpure®Meldin®Norbond®NORFILM™NORGLIDE®Norseal®OmniSeal®ONESUIT®PharmaFluor®PharmaPure®Pure-Fit®RENCOL®Rulon®Sani-Tech®SHEERFILL®SHEERGARD®Solar Gard®ThermaCool®Thermalbond®TYGON®VERSILON™VueLife®All ProductsBackAll ProductsALL PRODUCTSAdhesive TapesArchitectural FilmsArchitectural MembraneAutomotive FilmsBearingsBeltingBioprocess ContainersCap Liner, Stopper and Plunger LaminatesCell Culture BagsChemical Protective ClothingNorFilm™ConnectionsCryopreservation ProductsCustom CB SheltersConductosElectrical InsulationFabricated SystemsFiltration SystemsFluid Transfer AssembliesFluoropolymer FilmsFoam Bonding
TapesFoam in Place Gasketing Heat Seal EquipmentHoses and FittingsInsulation BlanketsLaboratory ProductsMedical ComponentsMedical Release LinersNoise ProofingPharmaceutical Systems Protective HoodsPumps, Valves, Fittings and ManifoldsRadomesSealing and Cushioning FoamsSealing SolutionsSealsSpecialty ClosuresStructural Glazing Spacer TapeThermoforming CompositesTolerance RingsTubingWear and Friction ControlAerospaceBackAerospaceAEROSPACEApplicationsBackApplicationsAirframeAPUGas Turbine EngineRadar and TelecommunicationsSpace ExplorationBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeCOVISON™FluoroWrap®Meldin®OmniSeal®SHEERGARD®VERSILON™ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesBeltingDuctingElectrical InsulationFabricated SystemsFluoropolymer FilmsWear and Friction ControlHoses and FittingsInsulation BlanketsRadomesSealing SolutionsSealsThermoforming CompositesTubingAutomotiveBackAutomotiveAUTOMOTIVEBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeCOVISON™DynaFoam®Meldin®NorBond®NORFILM™NORGLIDE®Norseal®RENCOL®Solar Gard®ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesAutomotive FilmsBearingsBeltingCoated, Sputtered and Laminated FilmsFabricated SystemsFluoropolymer FilmsFoam Bonding
TapesFoam in Place Gasketing Sealing and Cushioning FoamsSealing SolutionsSealsTolerance RingsApplicationsBackApplicationsAutomotive ExteriorAutomotive InteriorEngine ComponentsConsumerBackConsumerCONSUMERBrandsBackBrandsGreen Glue®NORGLIDE®RENCOL®Solar Gard®TYGON®VERSILON™ProductsBackProductsAutomotive FilmsBearingsHoses and FittingsNoise ProofingTolerance RingsTubingApplicationsBackApplicationsBicyclesInk Jet PrintingLawn and Garden Equipment Fuel TransferResidential HVACElectronicsBackElectronicsELECTRONICSBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeFURON®FluoroWrap®NORFILM™Norseal®SHEERGARD™ThermalCool®TYGON®RENCOL®VERSILON™ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesBeltingCoated, Sputtered and Laminated FilmsElectrical InsulationFabricated SystemsFluoropolymer FilmsHoses and FittingsPumps, Valves, Fittings and ManifoldsRadomesSealing and Cushioning Foam TubingApplicationsBackApplicationsDielectric isolationElectronic DisplayGround-based Radar ProtectionHard Disk DrivesMicroelectronicsSemiconductor EncapsulationEnergyBackEnergyENERGYBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeFluoroWrap®OmniSeal®ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesBeltingElectrical InsulationFabricated SystemsFluoropolymer FilmsSealsApplicationsBackApplicationsFSOFuel CellsNatural Gas Expansion Joint MaterialsPhotovoltaic FrontsheetSolar Thermal CollectionSub SeaWind Turbine ManufacturingFood & BeverageBackFood & BeverageFOOD & BEVERAGEBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®TYGON®VERSILON™ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesBeltingFabricated SystemsHoses and FittingsTubingApplicationsBackApplicationsFood and Beverage DispensingFood ProcessingPackagingQuick Service RestaurantsRaw Milk CollectionHabitatBackHabitatHABITATBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®COVISON™DynaFoam®Green Glue®NorBond®NORFILM™Norseal®SHEERFILL®Solar Gard®Thermalbond®ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesArchitectural FilmsArchitectural MembraneCoated, Sputtered and Laminated FilmsFabricated SystemsFoam Bonding
TapesFoam in Place GasketingNoise ProofingSealing and Cushioning FoamsSealing SolutionsStructural Glazing Spacer TapeApplicationsBackApplicationsExterior Roofing SystemsFaçadeGlass & MirrorsHabitat SealingPVC Welding ReleaseUtilitiesIndustrialBackIndustrialINDUSTRIALBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFAB®CHEMFILM®CHR® TapeNORFILM™NorBond®Norseal®Rulon®TYGON®VERSILON™ProductsBackProductsAdhesive TapesBeltingCoated, Sputtered and Laminated FilmsFabricated SystemsFluoropolymer FilmsFoam Bonding
TapesHoses and FittingsSealing and Cushioning FoamsSealsTubingApplicationsBackApplicationsAppliancesChemical DispensingCompressorsDiaphragms and GasketsPolymer ProcessingProcess Belting and CastingSurface ProtectionPumps and ValvesSensor Diffusion MembranesLife SciencesBackLife SciencesLIFE SCIENCESBrandsBackBrandsBio-Simplex®C-Flex®CHEMFILM®KryoSure®Labpure®NORFILM™OmniSeal®PharmaPure®PharmaFluor®Pure-Fit®Rulon®Sani-Tech®TYGON®VERSILON™VueLife®ProductsBackProductsBioprocess ContainersCap Liner, Stopper and Plunger LaminatesCell Culture BagsCoated, Sputtered and Laminated FilmsConnectionsCryopreservation ProductsFiltration SystemsFluid Transfer AssembliesFluoropolymer FilmsHeat Seal EquipmentHoses and FittingsLaboratory ProductsMedical ComponentsMedical Release LinersPharmaceutical SystemsPumps, Valves, Fittings and ManifoldsSealsSpecialty ClosuresTubingApplicationsBackApplicationsAnalytical InstrumentationCell CultureCell TherapyEnvironmental Fluid Analysis and SamplingMedical ComponentsSurgical ToolsSurface ProtectionSafety & ProtectionBackSafety & ProtectionSAFETY & PROTECTIONBrandsBackBrandsCHEMFILM®CORETECH®NORFILM™ONESUIT®ProductsBackProductsONESUIT®Custom CB SheltersFluoropolymer FilmsProtective HoodsApplicationsBackApplicationsChemical ContainmentExpansion JointsHuman Remain BagsMultipurpose Hydration SystemsProtective SheltersSurface ProtectionBusinessesBackBusinessesBearingsFabricsFilmsTape SolutionsLife SciencesProcess SystemsSealsAerospaceNews & EventsCareersAbout UsContact Us
You are hereHome Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
1) PRIVACY POLICY
Effective Date: November 20th, 2017
The institutional website accessible at the address www.plastics.saint-gobain.com (the “Site”) is owned and edited by Saint-Gobain Performance Plastics Inc.(the “Company”) with its registered office at 31500 Solon Road, Ohio 44139 USA. The Site uses several processing operations which purpose is to ensure the communication and exchange of information with users (e.g. forms for comments, newsletter, etc.). These operations may require the user to provide personal data, such as, for example, their email address. This privacy policy describes Company’s practices with respect to the processing of such data.
These processing operations notably make it possible to: provide, administer and communicate with you about products, services, events, surveys and promotions by Company or our affiliates (including by sending you marketing communications).
Types of Data Collected
Various types of personal data may be collected by the Site, including asking you to provide: name, email and or phone number, country, company title when requested to fill out our forms, by automated means, such as cookies and usage tracking; and by obtaining information from third parties, such as data vendors.
When you access our internet sites or use our mobile applications, we may automatically (that is, not by registration) collect additional data (such as type of Internet browser, IP address, and operating system used, domain name of the internet site which directed you to our site, number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, information on your interaction with the site).
How Company Uses the Collected Data
The collected data:
Are for internal use only and are directed to those responsible for handling the user's request,
Are used to provide and improve the Site and personalize the user experience,
May be used to detect, prevent and mitigate fraudulent or illegal activity,
May be used for any other purpose we describe when we collect the information, and
Are kept only as long as necessary to carry out the purposes defined above.
Any personal data that may be collected through the use of this Site will be processed and stored by the Company in accordance with the applicable law of jurisdiction.
How Company May Share the Collected Data
Company may disclose personal data collected through the use of this Site:
To Company’s third party service providers that assist Company in the operation of its business and the Site,
To a purchaser or successor entity in connection with the sale, merger, assignment or other transfer of Company or any of its affiliates, or line of business or product of Company or any of its affiliates,
To respond to law enforcement requests or where Company determines that disclosure is required by applicable laws, court orders or government regulations,
To enforce our Terms of Use, to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Company or others, and
If you have consented to the disclosure.
Do Not Track
The Site does not support Do Not Track at this time. Do Not Track is a privacy preference that you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across websites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For details, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit www.donottrack.us.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Company may change this Privacy Policy from time to time in its discretion. Company will post such changes to this web page and note the date of the most recent revision of the Privacy Policy above. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently to be informed of how Company is collecting, using, retaining, protecting, disclosing, and transferring your information. Your continued use of the Site after Company posts any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of such changes.
Access to Your Personal Data; Questions and Comments
We will provide you with reasonable access to your personal data in accordance with relevant laws, including by making reasonable efforts to provide you with the opportunity to update your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personal information. For any questions or comments about this privacy policy or your personal data, please send a written request to:]
31500 Solon Rd. Solon, Ohio 44139
Users are informed that their personal data be transferred to companies whose servers are located outside the European Union.
Saint-Gobain Performance Plastics Corp. and all its businesses and subsidiaries are affiliates of Saint-Gobain Corporation and adhere to its group's privacy policy.  The group's California Resident's Notice is found at www.saint-gobain-northamerica.com/california-privacy-policy.
Refer to our Cookie Policy
